* Toggle search modal

Menu

* Resources
* News
* Features
* Consultants
* Contact

* [
    
    Just getting started? Here’s what you need to know. Empower](https://defendinged.org/empower/) 
* [
    
    Found something and want to investigate? Expose](https://defendinged.org/expose/) 
* [
    
    You’re up and running, now what? Engage](https://defendinged.org/engage/) 

* [Collaborative for Academic, Social, and Emotional Learning (CASEL)](https://defendinged.org/report/casel/)

* [Something going on in your school we should know about? Report an Incident](https://defendinged.org/join-the-movement/report-an-incident/) 
* [Already working with an organization or community? Submit an Organization](https://defendinged.org/join-the-movement/submit-an-organization/) 
* [\[email protected\]](https://defendinged.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Find us via our social media

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.

We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE
------------------------------

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:

* Name
* Email address

Personal Information you provide to us may be shared with Parents Defending Education Action, a related non-profit 501(c)(4) organization.

LOG DATA
--------

We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

COOKIES
-------

Our website uses certain tags, log files, web beacons, pixels, and similar tracking technologies from third parties (collectively, “cookies”), of which you should be aware.

Cookies are text files containing small amounts of information that can be downloaded to your device when you visit a website. Cookies enable us to analyze how this Website is used and to monitor site performance, so we can create the best user experience. We may also use cookies to personalize language settings and to provide social media features.

We use cookies and device data such as information about your visit to our website, IP address, the URLs of the websites and pages you visit (before, during and after your visit to the Website) and the times and dates of such visits, information about the computer hardware and software you use, device identifier, location and time zone setting, even when you are not logged in. Also, PDE may place “cookies” on your computer or use other tracking technologies like web beacons and pixels, to access or store information and to recognize you on return visits to enable PDE to enhance your browsing experience, as well as to collect additional information about you.

We also may use that data to advertise information to you on other platforms such as Facebook and Instagram and other social media platforms. This processing is necessary for our legitimate interest to send you tailored marketing messages, client newsletters, and invitations to relevant events and seminars.

In addition to the cookies used by PDE and our service providers, some cookies are placed by third parties such as Google Analytics and Facebook, as described below. By using PDE’s Website, you agree to the use of cookies for the following purposes:

(1) _Essential Cookies._ These are essential in order to enable you to move around PDE’s Website and use its features, such as accessing secure areas of the website.

(2) _Performance and Analytics Cookies._ Google Analytics (“Analytics”) is Google’s free web analytics tool that helps us understand how our visitors engage with our website. Analytics collects information anonymously and, much like examining footprints in sand, it reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Analytics uses its own set of cookies to track visitor interactions. These cookies are used to store information, such as what time the current visit occurred, whether the visitor has been to the site before, and what site referred the visitor to the web page. Google Analytics customers can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve their website and how people find it. A different set of cookies is used for each website, and visitors are not tracked across multiple sites. Analytics customers are obliged to notify users of their use of analytics software. To disable this type of cookie, some browsers will indicate when a cookie is being sent and allow you to decline cookies on a case-by-case basis. In addition to declining cookies, you can also install the Google Analytics Opt-out Add-on in your browser, which prevents Google Analytics from collecting information about your website visits. You can also opt out by clicking [**here**](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

(3) _Advertising, Direct Marketing, and Lead Generation_. We use social media platforms to assist us in our advertising and marketing efforts, including Facebook and Instagram.

(4) _Functionality Cookies._ These remember the choices you make, such as language options or your current region. These cookies help to make your visit more personal.

You can block or disable cookies on your device at any time by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. You can also delete the cookies that are stored on your device. However, blocking, disabling, or deleting cookies may limit your ability to view all the pages of this Website or use online services that require registration. You may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting their [**Ad Settings page**](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated). You may also opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies at the [**Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page**](https://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1). You can find more information about cookies at [**www.allaboutcookies.org**](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [**www.youronlinechoices.com**](https://www.youronlinechoices.com/).

SERVICE PROVIDERS
-----------------

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

SECURITY
--------

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.

COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS
--------------------

We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
------------------------------

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

CONTACT US
----------

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.

Stay Informed

Sign Up for Updates
-------------------

* * *

* Name\*
    
    First  Last 
    
* Email\*
    
* Address\*
    
     ZIP / Postal Code  
    
* CAPTCHA
    
* Comments
    
    This field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.

Parents Defending Education is a 501(c)(3) charitable organization and charitable contributions are tax-deductible.  
Our federal tax identification number is 86-1596460.

* ### Email Us
    
    [\[email protected\]](https://defendinged.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

* ### For 990 Inquiries, Email
    
    [\[email protected\]](https://defendinged.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Search  Search

© Parents Defending Education 2024 | [Privacy Policy](https://defendinged.org/privacy-policy/)

##### Search

Close ×

Search  Search

Close
